DEJAY ODUJOKO

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

+8167854438



dejavxtrem@hotmail.com



Fayetteville, AR



linkedin.com/in/Adedeji-odujoko



EDUCATION

ENTERPRISE SYSTEMS, MS University of Arkansas, Arkansas 2016 - 2017

INTERNATIONAL BUSINESS, MSC Conventry University, UK 2012 - 2014

> SOFTWARE ENGINEERING General Assembly

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Ruby/Rails

Javascript

Python

HTML5/CSS

Nodejs/Express

Mongodb/Postgres

React/React-Native

CERTIFICATIONS

(Clarify & Harmony)

Code Academy (Build Front-End Web Apps from Scratch) Code Academy (Build Web APIs from Scratch) Code Academy (Build Websites from Scratch) Cleo Certified Clarify EDI Developer

PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

An innovative and motivated individual with the ability work in a fast paced, multi-tasking environment and produce a high standard of work. Competence with multiple programming languages, including JavaScript, Python, NodeJS, React, React-native, HTML, CSS, Linux. Experience with Electronic Data Interchange (EDI) in IT and EDI translations. Extensive exposure to the full B2B integration process, Enterprise Applications, and communication protocols.

EXPERIENCE

JBHUNT TRANSPORT | ARKANSAS | 2019 - Present

EDI ANALYST

- Conducts minor Electronic Data Interchange mapping enhancements and
- Assists Electronic Data Interchange admins in any functions where necessary
- Map and convert X12 documents to XML, JSON, and CSV for inbound and outbound document series.
- Assists in verification of communication connections.
- Integrate with trading partners via REST, SOAP and EDI.

General Assembly | Remote | 2019 - 2020

Software Engineer

- Built Real World applications of web development principles and best practices.
- Built full stack web applications with multiple CRUD capabilities and employing DOM manipulation.
- Integrated web applications with third-party API as needed.
- Developed both on the Front end and back End.
- Develop wireframe and sitemap mockups to illustrate possible solution.

SUPPLYPIKE | ARKANSAS | 2017 - 2019

INTEGRATION DEVELOPER

- Analyze and translate business requirements into technical solutions.
- Develop and implement solutions to integrate applications across SupplyPike.
- Map and convert X12 documents to XML, JSON, and CSV for inbound and outbound document series.
- Integrate with trading partners via REST, SOAP and EDI.

EDI Academy (EDI 850, 856, ASN and UCC-128 labels)

EDI Academy (EDI Enveloping & Structure)

EDI Academy (EDI connectivity AS2, VAN, FTP)

CompTIA A+ Certified Technician Portfolio: http://dejayodujoko.herokuapp.com

EXPERTISE

Web Development
B2B Integration
Enterprise Sysytems
EDI Translation
Web Application
EDIHQ Translation Software
Cleo Harmony and Clarify

INTERESTS

Gaming
Traveling
Long Tennis
Sports (Soccer)

EXPERIENCE

ZEBRA TECHNOLOGIES | ARKANSAS | 2016 - 2017

BENCH REPAIR TECHNICIAN

- Performed changes and retrofits on customer's equipment in conjunction with routine maintenance.
- Accurate and timely return of repair paperwork and parts kits.
- Diagnosed most equipment problems using appropriate tools, test equipment, and documentation.

K12 UK Limited | UNITED KINGDOM | 2015 – 2015 FINANCE AND ADMIN ASSISTANT

- Processed and reconcile purchase and sales ledger transactions and monthly head office bank reconciliations.
- Maintained computerised and manual bookkeeping accounting and recording filing systems through the use of FMS and SAGE 50 Accounts 2014
- Ensured all purchase invoices are properly coded, posted to the ledger and authorised for payment.

GOTBOX22 STORAGE | UNITED KINGDOM | 2013 - 2014

ACCOUNT ASSISTANT

- Processed payments and documents such as invoices.
- Journal vouchers, employee reimbursements, and statements.
- Calculate rates paid for purchases and all price extensions.
- Review on-line transactions for changes and accuracy and corrects errors.
- Disbursed funds using manual/local warrants or petty cash and makes changes according to specific instructions..